{"status":"Success","data":{"quiz_datas":[{"question_no":"595","question":"2012 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d26\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d47\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7b","option2":"\u0d0b\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d18\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7a \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d7b","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"248","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d07\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b \u0d1f\u0d42\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d. \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d32","option2":"\u0d07\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02","option4":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"475","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d41\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24","option4":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"381","question":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f, \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24, \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d28, \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d47\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d02, \u0d13\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e, \u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d24\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02","option1":"\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"282","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d34","option2":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7e","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d35\u0d39\u0d43\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"410","question":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d35\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f :","option1":"10 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 1000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","option2":"20 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 10000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","option3":"20 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 2000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","option4":"20 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 20000 Hz \u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"261","question":"\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d12.\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d1f\u0d3f. \u0d09\u0d37","option3":"\u0d37\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d7a","option4":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"141","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d42\u0d7c ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d32\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d","option4":"\u0d15\u0d48\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d32\u0d02 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"133","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d35\u0d31 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ?","option1":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"430","question":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d","option1":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b C","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b B","option3":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b D","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b A","answer":"3"}]},"code":"100"}
